# GABOR CZINEGE

6365 Green Valley Circle, Culver City, CA 90230 x 310-754-0037 x gabor.czinege@yahoo.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabor-c-4445263a/

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced CompTA A+ certified IT professional with over 7 years of experience providing software, hardware, client/server and networking technical support. Demonstrated strengths in implementing and improving IT solutions for worldwide multi-location multilingual high-security businesses. Proven, reliable success in troubleshooting computer systems, optimizing access and utilization of shared information and improving the efficiency of IT and business operations.

#### SKILLS

- System administration
- Printers
- Networking
- ITILv3

- Microsoft Servers
- VMware
- PowerShell

#### WORK HISTORY

## DXC Technology / Service Desk Technician II, 09/2015 to 05/2019

**Commerzbank AG** (supporting Germany from Budapest – Hungary)

- Troubleshoot, document, and diagnose system issues, including reviewing event logs and system logs.
- Demonstrated professionalism with end users at all times as the single point of contact.
- Maintenance of the printer database of over 10.000 printers on Windows Server 2012 R2 / 2016.
- Perform analysis, diagnosis, and resolution of complex desktop computer, operating system, application software and hardware technologies, remote access technologies, via Remote Desktop and VMware, network related, and associated problems with little to no direct supervision.
- Help non-IT coworkers by providing faster, more efficient methods in their daily routine with my technical knowledge that made the team's productivity 25% higher within 6 months.
- Technologies, used software: HP Service Manager, HP Web Jetadmin, C# .NET software I developed, Windows 10, Windows 2012 Server, VMware, vSphere, inhouse administrative web applications for DHCP, password resets, and diagnostic software.

## Lexmark / Dispatch Team Lead, 08/2011 to 05/2015

**BASF** (Ludwigshafen – Germany)

- Establishing communication between project management and team.
- Direct management and coordination of team, performance management.
- Managing delivery of printers and maintenance/repair services to achieve agreed end results (SLA).
- Ensuring smooth delivery and operation of IT services by monitoring systems performance.
- With my efficiency, experience and expertise the company's SLA breaches dropped from 30% to almost zero. According to the team, the stress level of the workplace got unmeasurably low.
- Technologies, used software: Microsoft Dynamics NAV with custom scripts.

# HP Enterprise / Desktop Support Technician II, 03/2007 to 06/2010

Eli Lilly & Co., Continental (supporting Zone 2 EMEA from Miskolc – Hungary)

- Handle and troubleshoot, follow up, and close daily 30-35 incident tickets dispatched from Tier I, including domain account creation, Active Directory groups and rights management, and password resets.
- Provide support to users who are experienced problems with their computers/printers/scanners/phones or software. Build the knowledge base of the new team.
- *Technologies, used software:* HP Service Center, Remedy, Windows XP/7, Windows Server 2003/2008, AD, PS, Event Viewer, inhouse applications for RSA Token resets, security applications.

### **EDUCATION**

- Software Development & Mathematics University of Debrecen
- Business IT & Accounting Karl Keleti High School

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

• CompTIA A+ Technician